[
  {
    "question": "The html code executed by ________",
    "answer": "browser"
  },
  {
    "question": "HTML files are saved with which extension _______",
    "answer": ".html"
  },
  {
    "question": "Write the closing tag in HTML _______",
    "answer": "</html>"
  },
  {
    "question": "The root element of an HTML document is the ___________ tag.",
    "answer": "<html>"
  },
  {
    "question": "The section that contains meta-information about the document ______",
    "answer": "<head>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Write the opening tag in HTML _______",
    "answer": "<html>"
  },
  {
    "question": "Content that is visible on the web page is written inside the ___________.",
    "answer": "<body>"
  },
  {
    "id": "html_b_8",
    "question": "What is the tag used to represent the HTML version ____________",
    "answer": "<!DOCTYPE>"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the tag display the title of the web page ____________",
    "answer": "<title>"
  },
  {
    "question": "The collection of web pages __________",
    "answer": "website"
  }
]
